

MARCIN KURTZ

+48 662 466 302

kurtz.marcin@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/marcin-kurtz/github.com/mkIO

BIO

Senior Fullstack Engineer and Lead Developer with over 8 years' experience in delivering modern web applications utilizing multiple frameworks (React, Angular) with the latest .NET framework, together with implementing DevOps solutions targeting Azure Cloud and on-premise solutions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Engineering | Informatics2011 – 2015Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Silesian University of TechnologyGliwice, PolandMaster of Engineering | Applied Mathematics and Cryptography2007 – 2014Faculty of Applied Mathematics, Silesian University of TechnologyGliwice, Poland

WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Developer 01/2021 - present

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Designing the architecture of software products and APIs, software development, implementing devops infrastructure, bug fixing and refactoring, developing new business critical features, core review
- **Technologies**: : C#, TypeScript, Powershell, .NET Core/5/6, React, REST API Services, Azure Cloud Services/Functions, Azure SDK, Azure SQL Server, Azure Service Bus, Terraform

Senior Software Developer

07/2018 - 01/2021

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Designing the architecture of software products and APIs, software development, bug fixing and refactoring, developing new business critical features, code review
- **Technologies**: .NET Core, Angular, Powershell, REST API Services, Azure Services, Azure DevOps and Octopus Deployment pipelines, C#, TypeScript, Azure SQL Server, Azure Service Bus, OData Services

Medium Software Developer

07/2014 - 07/2018

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- **Responsibilites**: Application development, bug fixing, developing new business critical features, refactoring, code review, implementing backend services
- Technologies: ASP.NET, NET 4.7, WCF, XSLT with XML, SQL Server, VB.NET, C#, Chef

Junior Software Developer

07/2013 - 06/2014

Future Processing Sp. z o.o.

Gliwice, Poland

- Application development
- Technologies: ASP.NET, NET 4, WCF, SQL Server, XML with XML, VB.NET, C#, JavaScript

CERTIFICATES

AZ-204: Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure	01/2022
Developing Solutions for Microsoft Azure	
70-486: Developing ASP .NET 4.5 MVC Web Applications Developing ASP .NET 4.5 MVC Web Applications	12/2015
70-480: Programming in HTML 5 with JavaScript and CSS3 HTML 5 with JavaScript and CSS3	07/2015
M101N: MongoDB for .NET Developers Developing MongoDB solutions for .NET applications	06/2015

Languages: Polish (native), English (B1), French (A1)

Document Creation: Microsoft Office Suite, LaTex, Markdown

Technologies: .NET, Microsoft Azure, DevOps, ASP.NET MVC, C#, Cryptography, HTML, XML, LaTeX, XAML, WCF, Domain Driven Design (DDD), Chef, Terraform, Entity Framework, SOAP, .NET Core, .NET 5/6, CQRS, Telerik Kendo UI, ASP.NET Core, ASP.NET Web API, Code Review, ASP.NET Core MVC, ASP.NET WebForms, CSS, jQuery, MS SQL, Visual Studio, JavaScript, Ajax, Linux, MySQL, SQLite, WPF, MongoDB, NoSQL, RabbitMQ, REST, WebSocket, JSON, HTML5, Git, node.js, Reactive Programming, SASS, ASP.NET SignalR, Aspect oriented programming, OOP, Test Driven development (TDD), Unit Tests, Vim, Visual Studio Code, Windows Server, Angular, Defensive Programming, Design Patterns, Docker, Identity Server, Jenkins CI Server, Octopus, Azure DevOps, Jira, Microservices, Oauth2, RestSharp, Web Services, Windows Services, Bootstrap, Build Scripts, Google APIs, Google Cloud Platform, React JS, Redux, Roslyn, RxJS, SQL Server, Swagger, TypeScript, Xamarin.Forms, .NET (desktop), Amazon Web Services (AWS), Android development, Mobile development (other), Software Architecture, Web frontend (other), Xamarin,